爸爸希望我们继承他的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things, Family business.
这里有治疗宿罪的好药物
There's a really good cure for a hangover.
就是用烟灰缸装三明治给你吃
It's a greasy pork sandwich served up in a dirty ashtray.
哦 我恨你 我知道你会的
Oh, I hate you. - I know you do.
我们别再玩那些无聊的游戏了 什么无聊的游戏？
We're not gonna start that. Start what?
那些恶作剧 那很愚蠢而且没完没了
That prank stuff. It's stupid and it always escalates.
萨姆 那又怎么样？
What's the matter, Sam?
你是害怕你的洗发水里又出现虫子吧？
Afraid you're gonna get a little Nair in your shampoo?
好 你记住 是你要开始的
Just remember you started it.
那个 是我干的
What the-? One: me.
这就是你的水平啊？你太弱了 你这个变态
- That's all you got? That's weak. - You're a frigging jerk.
你闻起来象一只掉在马桶里的 小鸡
- You smell like a toilet. - Chicken.
变态 贱人
- Jerk. - Bitch.
闭嘴 白痴
- Shut up. - Wuss.
贱人 变态
- Bitch. - Jerk.
是你要继续的 长毛
Well, bring it on, baldy.
请问
Excuse me.
你走丢了吗？
Are you lost?
没有 我一直在等你 教授
No, I've been waiting for you, professor.
- 哦 你是我教过的学生吗？- 你不记得我了？
- Ah, you're in one of my classes? - Don't you recognize me?
我教的班级太多了
Well...
不管怎么说 我的办公时间是在 星期二和星期四的上午
They're big classes.Anyway, my office hours are Tuesday and Thursday mornings.
是吗？我只是… 希望能见你一面
Really? I was hoping I could see you now.
那 既然你这么有诚意 进来吧
Well, since you asked so nicely, come on.
这张照片真帅
Such a handsome photo.
那是很久以前的事了
That old thing?
那 我能帮你点什么吗？期末论文写得怎么样了？
So, what can I do for you? How's the Anscombe paper coming?
教授 我…
Uh, professor, I...
我想跟您说句实话
I have a confession to make.
哦？说什么？
Oh, what's that?
我并不是您的学生
I'm not really one of your students.
是吗
Really?
那 你为什么要到这儿来？
Then why are you here?
我看我还是走吧 等等
- Maybe I should just go. - Wait.
我明白了
I get it.
我了解你的感受 这是发自内心的
I understand how you're feeling and it's only natural.
你很年轻又天真活泼
You are young and wide-eyed...
而我站在这里 在某种程度上也算是个名人
and I'm somewhat of a celebrity around here.
别误会我 你真的很漂亮
Don't get me wrong, you're a very beautiful girl...
但我又不忍心占你的便宜
but it would be wrong of me to take advantage of you.
我只是 呃… 我只是太尊重你了
I just, uh... I just respect you too much.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
怎么了？
What?
你不再喜欢我了吗？
Don't you like me anymore?
你不再需要我了吗？
Don't you want me?
[邪恶力量 第2季第15集]
(一周后)
伙计 你介不介意不在我床上吃那些东西
Dude, you mind not eating those on my bed?
不 我不介意
No, I don't mind.
- 调查的如何了？- 想知道进行的如何了？
- How's the research going? - You know how it's going?
慢
Slow.
该死的你知道如何才能进行的更快吗？
You know how it would go a heck of a lot faster?
如果我有电脑的话
If I had my computer.
- 你能调小点声吗？拜托 - 好 当然可以
- Can you turn that down, please? - Yeah, absolutely.
你知道吗？
You know what?
也许你应该去别的地方呆会
Maybe you should just go somewhere for a while, huh?
嘿 我很想去 这主意很不错…
Hey, I'd love to. That's a great idea.
- 不幸的是 我的车他奶奶的完蛋了 - 我告诉过你 这不关我的…
- Unfortunately, my car's screwed to hell. - I told you I had nothing to do
- 嘿 鲍比 嘿 - 小伙子们
Hey, Bobby. - Boys.
嘿 鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
这么快能再见到你们真好
It's good to see you again so soon.
是的 呃… 谢谢你能赶来
Yeah, uh, thanks for coming.
快进来吧
Come on in.
感谢上帝你来了
Thank God you're here.
那么 呃… 你们在电话里想跟我谈什么？
So, what didn't you wanna talk to me on the phone about?
是关于我们正在做的一些事情
It's this job we're working we
我们不敢确定你会相信我们
We weren't sure you'd believe us.
我能相信很多东西
Well, I can believe a lot.
是 是的 我知道 只是我们从来没有见过这样的事情
No, yeah, yeah. I know. It's just, we've never seen anything like it.
连类似的都没有
Not even close.
所以我们认为可以利用一些其他人的经验
We thought we could use some fresh eyes.
为何你们不从开始讲起？
Well, why don't you begin at the beginning?
没问题 好的 请坐
Yeah. Um, all right, please.
那么…
So...
是从我们找到的一条讣告开始的
it all started when we caught wind of an obit.
你瞧 一个教授脸朝下… 从四楼的窗户掉了下来
See, a professor took a nosedive from a fourth-story window.
校园传说那是个闹鬼的房子
Only there's a campus legend that the building's haunted.
所以 我们就假扮成当地报纸的记者
So we pretexted as reporters from the local paper.
是的 我们都是教授课上的学生
We both had the professor for Ethics and Morality.
那么 为何你认为是他做的
Yeah? So why do you think he did it?
谁知道 他是有家室的 有妻子和孩子 他的书是个大手笔
Who knows? He was tenured, wife and kids, his book was, like, a really big deal.
话说回来 是谁说他一定是自杀的？
Then again, who's to say it was suicide?
- 珍 够了 - 那么… 还能是什么？
- Jen, come on. - Well, what else could it be?
- 你应该知道关于克劳福德礼堂的事情吧 - 不 事实上我不知道
- Well, you know about Crawford Hall. - No. I don't, actually.
那都是胡扯 那完全只是个当地的传说
It's a bunch of crap, a total urban legend.
希瑟的妈妈从前在这里上学… 而且她认识那个女孩
Yeah? Well, Heather's mom went to school here and she knew the girl.
等等 哪个女孩
Wait, what girl?
30年前 这个女孩和某个教授有私情
Like 30 years ago, this girl was having an affair with some professor.
他把她给甩了 她就跳楼自杀了
He broke it off. She jumped out the window and killed herself.
- 你知道她的名字吗？- 不知道
- You know her name? - No.
但是人们说她是从669号房间跳楼的
But they say she jumped from Room 669.
明白了吗？你把9倒过来看…
Get it? You turn the nine upside down.
所以 现在她在那座房子里面出没…
So now she haunts the building.
如果谁看到了她… 就没法活着再讲这个传说了
And anyone who sees her, they don't live to tell the tale.
如果没有人能够活着讲出这个传说… 那么 这个传说是怎么来的？
Well, if no one lives to tell the tale, then how does the tale get told?
柯蒂斯 闭嘴
Curtis, shut up.
知道吗 非常感谢你们 失陪了
You know what? Uh, thanks a lot, guys. Excuse me.
迪恩 你在… 你在喝什么？
Dean, what are you...? What are you drinking?
我不知道 伙计 我想这叫做
I don't know, man. I think they're called purple nurples. Ha, ha.
我想我们应该去检查一下教授的办公室
I think maybe we should go check out the professor's office.
哦不 不 不行 我现在不行
Oh, no, no, no. I can't right now.
我现在已经钓上一只迷人的小野猫了
I got some... I've got a feisty little wildcat on the hook.
我已经准备好了… 嘿嘿… 让她爽爽
I'm about to, zip, reel her in.
- 我介绍给你认识 - 迪恩…
- I'll introduce you. - Dean..
斯塔拉 斯塔拉
Starla. Starla, hey.
这是我航天飞机上的副驾驶员 汤姆少校 汤姆少校 这是斯塔拉
This is my shuttle copilot, Major Tom. Major Tom, Starla.
他帅吧？
Mm, ha, ha. Enchanté.
嗨
Hi.
对不起 我只是把酒给压下去
Sorry. Just trying to keep my liquor down. Ha, ha.
干的不错
Yeah. Good job.
嘿 有个好消息
Hey, good news.
她有一个妹妹
She's got a sister.
- 等一下 - 怎么了？
- Hold on a minute. - What?
拜托 伙计 事情不是这样的
Come on, dude. That's not how it happened.
不是吗？所以说你从来没有喝过
No? So you never drank a purple nurple?
那个也许喝过 不过…
Yeah, maybe that.
我从来不会说像"迷人的小野猫"一样的话 而且她的名字不是斯塔拉
I don't say things like "feisty little wildcat." Her name wasn't Starla.
那名字是什么？
Then what was it?
我不知道 不过她是一个优雅的女人
I don't know. But she was a classy chick.
她是个读人类学和民俗文化的学的大学毕业生
She was a grad student: Anthropology and Folklore.
我们想说的是关于那个当地的鬼传说
We were talking about local ghost stories.
为了…
Here's to..
为了我们自己干杯
Here's to us.
我的上帝啊 你太有魅力了
My God, you are attractive.
谢谢 但是现在没有时间说这些
Thanks, but no time for that now.
你得跟我讲讲关于那个传说的事情
You need to tell me about this urban legend.
拜托了 时间不多
Please, lives are at stake.
对不起 我只是… 无法集中精神
I'm sorry, I just...I can't even concentrate.
就像是只能愣着神…
It's like staring...
盯着你 无法自拔
into the sun.
迪恩 你认为你在做着什么？
Dean, what do you think you're doing?
萨姆 拜托
Sam, please.
如果你不介意的话 给我5分钟
If you wouldn't mind, just give me five minutes here.
迪恩 这是一个很严肃的调查
Dean, this is a very serious investigation.
我们没有时间给你亲亲我我
We don't have time for any of your blah-blah blah-blah.
亲亲我我
Blah-blah blah-blah.
亲亲我我 亲亲我我
Blah, blah blah blah!
亲亲我我 亲亲我我 亲亲我我
Blah, blah-blah-blah blah.
亲亲我我
Blah!
够了 这个是真正发生的事情
Right, and that's how it really happened?
- 我不会那样说话 迪恩 - 对我来说你会那样说话
- I don't sound like that. - That's how you sound like to me.
好吧 你们两个到底怎么了？
Okay, what's going on with you two?
没事 什么事都没有
Nothing. It's nothing.
快说 你们像对老夫妻一样吵吵闹闹
Come on. Now, you're bickering like an old married couple.
不对 知道么 老夫妻是可以离婚的
No. See, married couples can get divorced.
我和他？我们就像… 呃… 畸形连着屁股的婴儿
Me and him? We're like, uh, Siamese twins.
- 是连体婴儿 - 看 明白我的意思了吗？
- It's conjoined twins. - See what I mean?
听着 这…
Look, it...
我们只是被搞的焦头烂额 精疲力竭 仅此而已
We've just been on the road for too long. Tight quarters, all that.
不用担心
Don't worry about it.
好的
Okay.
那么 我们继续 我们认为这可能是鬼
So anyway, we figured it might be a haunting...
所以我们便去检查凶案现场
so we went to check out the scene of the crime.
你在这里工作多久了？我已经在这里擦了六年的楼梯了
So How long you been working here? I've been mopping for six years.
我们到了 伙计们
There you go, guys.
那东西是做什么用的？
What the heck's that for?
只是用来寻找墙里的电线
Just finding wires in the walls.
哦
Ah, well...
不知道你们为什么要给这个办公室配线
Not sure why you're wiring up this office.
不会对教授有什么作用了
Not gonna do the professor much good.
- 为什么那样说？- 他死了
- Why's that? - He's dead.
哦 发生什么事了？
Oh, what happened?
他就从那个窗户掉了下去 就是那个
He went out that window right there.
是吗？
- Yeah?
- 你那天晚上在工作吗？- 我找到的他
- Were you working that night? - I'm the one who found him.
你看到事情经过了吗？没有
You see it happen? Nope.
我只看到他进来这里 而且… 呃…
I just saw him come up here and, uh...
- 好吧 - 怎么了？
- Well... - What?
他不是一个人
He wasn't alone.
他和谁一起？
Who was he with?
行了 我只吃了一个 也许是两个…
Come on. I ate one, maybe two.
我只是随口说说 行吗？
Just let me tell it, okay?
他和一个年轻的女人一起
He was with a young lady.
我跟警察讲了那个女人 但是 我猜他们没有找到她
I told the cops about her, but, uh, I guess they never found her.
你看到那个女人进来 对吗？
You saw this girl go in, huh?
那么你有看到她出去吗？
But did you ever see her come out?
现在你们提醒我了 没有
Now that you mention it, no.
你从前见过她吗 在这周围？
You ever see her before around?
- 不是她 - 那是什么意思？
- Well, not her. - What do you mean?
我不想去毁谤中伤一个去世的人 但是… 呃
I don't mean to cast aspersions on a dead guy...
这里的"道德先生"…
but, uh, Mr. Morality here?
他带过许多女孩子上来过
He brought a lot of girls up here.
比厕所里面的马桶还多
Got more ass than a toilet seat.
再多问一下 这个房子 只有四层 对吗？
One more thing. Uh, this building, it only has four stories, right?
- 是的 - 所以这里不会有669号房间
- Yeah. - So there wouldn't be a Room 669?
当然没有
Of course not.
为什么这样问？
Why do you ask?
只是好奇
Ah, just curious.
- 谢谢 - 没什么
- Thanks. - Yeah.
没有电动势反应 这点很确定
Well, no traces of EMF, that's for sure.
而且关于那个669号房间 都是一派胡言
And that Room 669 is a load of crap.
那么 你怎么想的？教授只是跳楼自杀？
So, what do you think, the professor's just a jumper?
- 传说只是个传说？- 我不知道
- Legend's just a legend? - I don't know.
看门人提到的那个女人 有点问题
I mean, the girl the janitor described, that's pretty weird.
是的
Yeah.
我们应该去查查那座房子的历史记录
We ought to check out the history of the building.
- 看看有没有女孩子跳楼摔死在那儿 - 是的 没错
- See if any coed ganked herself there. - Yeah, right.
伙计 你用过我的电脑吗？
Dude, were you on my computer?
- 没有 - 哦 真的吗？
- No. - Oh, really?
这里正定格在… 在… 在大波亚洲美女的网站上
Because it's frozen now on, uh, bustyasianbeauties.com.
迪恩…
Dean...
你能不能… 不要再碰我的东西了 好吗？
Would you just... Don't touch my stuff anymore, okay?
你为什么不去吃药控制好你的大脑强迫紊乱症？
Why don't you control your OCD?
你们找到关于那座房子的什么事了吗？
But did you dig up anything about the building?
或者是跳楼自杀的女学生？
Or on the suicidal coed?
没有 历史记录很干净
No. History's clean.
- 那么这不是闹鬼 - 也许不是
- Then it's not a haunting. - Maybe not.
跟你讲实话吧 我们也不是很确定
To tell you the truth, we're not sure.
你那是什么意思 你们不是很确定？
What do you mean you're not sure?
- 这很奇怪 - 什么很奇怪？
- Well, it's weird. - What's weird?
下一个部分 我们 呃… 事实上 我们不是亲眼看到事情的发生
This next part, we, uh, didn't see it happen ourselves exactly...
但是… 即使对我们来说 这真的也太奇怪了
but it's pretty frigging weird, even for us.
- 外星人？- 是的
- Aliens? - Yeah.
听着 如果他们是真的存在 他们肯定会来到地球袭击人类
Even if they are real, they're sure as hell not coming to Earth and swiping people.
嘿 相信我 我们知道的
Hey, believe me. We know.
向上帝保证 我这辈子都没有找到… 关于外星人绑架的任何证据
My whole life, I've never found evidence of an honest-to-God abduction.
这都是些恶作剧和异想天开的想法
It's all just cranks and pranks.
是的 我们当初也是这样认为的
Yeah, that's what we thought.
但是… 我们认为至少可以和那家伙谈谈
But we figured we'd at least talk to the guy.
嘿 你应该把那些"紫色奶头"全干了
Hey, you gotta give those purple nurples a shot.
发生什么了 柯蒂斯
So, what happened, Curtis?
你们不会相信我 没有人相信
You won't believe me. Nobody does.
给我们个机会
Give us a chance.
我不想我的话见报
I do not want this in the papers.
那么就删除记录
Off the record then.
我 呃…
I, uh...
我喝多了 然后
I blacked out...
我记不得有多久… 当我醒来的时候 我不知道我在哪
and I lost time and when I woke up, I don't know where I was.
然后呢？
Then what?
他们对我做了实验
They did tests on me.
然后 呃…
And, um...
他们 呃…
They, um...
他们给我做肠镜
They probed me.
他们给你做肠镜？
They probed you?
是的 他们给我做肠镜
Yeah, they probed me.
一次 又一次 再一次的…
Again and again, and again, and...
再一次的 再一次的 再一次的… 一次接一次的
And again and again, and again, and then one more time.
哦…
Yikes.
这还不是最惨的
No and that's not even the worst of it.
还能怎么惨？
How could it get any worse?
外星人把你强暴了？
Some alien made you his bitch.
他们…
They...
他们让我… 跟他们跳情舞
They made me slow dance.
你们又开始胡说八道了 对吧？
You guys are exaggerating again, huh?
没有
No.
那么那个小子就是个白痴
Then this frat boy is just nuts.
我们还不这么确定
We're not so sure.
我告诉你 迪恩
I'm telling you, Dean...
这是某种喷气飞机的引擎造成的
this was made by some kind of jet engine.
你是说某种茶杯形状的喷气飞机的引擎造成的？
What, you mean some saucer-shaped jet engine?
那还能是什么？
Well, what else could it be?
- 见鬼了 - 我不知道
- What the hell? - I don't know.
- 说真的 伙计 到底是什么？- 我不知道
- No, seriously, dude. What the hell? - I don't know.
我是说 最开始是闹鬼 现在来这个？
I mean, first the haunting, now this?
单从时间上来讲… 这一定有某种联系
The timing alone, there's gotta be a connection.
你是说在愤怒的灵魂和精装打扮的外星人之间？
You mean, between the angry spirit and the sexed-up E.T.?
什么样的联系有可能？
What could the connection possibly be?
但是我们又能做什么？
But what could we do?
所以我们只好继续找线索
So we just kept on digging.
你和这个叫柯蒂斯的人… 你们住在同一个房子里面？
So you and this guy Curtis, you're in the same house?
- 是的 - 你知道他发生了什么事了 对吗？
- Yeah. - You heard of what happened to him, right?
是的 他说是外星人 但是… 你明白的… 随便吧…
Yeah, he says it was aliens, but, you know, whatever.
听着 伙计 我…
Look, man...
我知道这一定会很难过
I know this all has to be so hard.
- 呃… 并不是很难过 - 但是我想让你知道…
- Um, not so much. - But I want you to know...
我会帮助你的
I'm here for you.
你真是个坚强的男子汉
You brave little soldier.
我理解你的痛苦
I acknowledge your pain.
来吧
Come here.
你应该被这个世界更加的关爱
You're too precious for this world.
我从来没有那样说
I never said that.
你经常讲那些娘娘腔的话
Well, you're always saying pansy stuff like that.
好吧 呃…
Well, um...
- 好的 呃… 谢谢 谢谢你的拥抱 - 没什么
- Yeah, uh, thanks. Thanks for the hug. - Yeah.
但是 呃… 我没事 真的
But, uh, I'm okay. Really.
告诉你实话
To tell you the truth...
无论柯蒂斯发生了什么 他都罪有应得
whatever happened to Curtis, he had it coming.
- 为什么？- 他是我们这儿的流氓大王
- Why's that? - He's our pledge master.
这个学期让我们尝尽了苦头 我们忍了很久了
Put us through hell this semester. Man, he got off on it.
所以 现在他知道我们的感觉了
So now he knows how we feel.
没关系了
It's okay.
还是一点头绪都没有
It still doesn't make a lick of sense.
但是 至少有一点联系了
But hey, at least there's one connection.
在哪之间？
Between what?
受害者
Victims.
教授和流氓男孩
The professor and the frat guy.
他们都是混蛋
Ha, they're both dicks.
那是联系？
That's a connection?
你有任何好的解释 我倒想听听
You got anything better to go on, I'd love to hear it.
- 我的笔记本电脑呢？- 我不知道
- Where's my laptop? - I don't know.
想想看… 一个喜欢玩弄女人的教授得到一个死去的女人
I mean, think about it. A philandering professor gets a dead girl.
流氓大王被非礼调戏
A pledge master gets hazed.
- 我放在这里来着 - 很显然你没有
- I left it in here. - Well, you obviously didn't.
我是说 这些惩罚 他们都很有戏剧性
I mean, these punishments, they're almost poetic.
实际上 这更有讽刺性 但是…
Actually, it'd be more like a limerick, but still...
好了 闹够了 你藏在哪了？
Okay, hilarious, ha, ha. Where'd you hide it?
- 你的电脑？- 是的 你藏在哪了？
- Your computer? - Yeah. Where'd you hide it?
- 我为什么要藏你的电脑？- 因为其他人不会
- Why would I take your computer? - No one else could have.
我们都锁着门 不用清洁工收拾房间
We keep the door locked. We never let any maids in.
看起来你弄丢了 爱读书的好学生
Look's like you lost it, Poindexter.
伙计 你知道吗？我已经忍了你很久了
Dude, you know something? I put up with a lot from you.
你在说什么？有我在身边是很开心的事
What? I'm a joy to be around.
是吗？你水池里面的臭袜子
Yeah? Your dirty socks in the sink.
- 你冰箱里的食物 - 我的食物怎么了
- Your food in the fridge. - What's wrong with my food?
那不再是食物了 迪恩
It's not food anymore, Dean.
- 这是达尔文主义 - 我喜欢它
- It's Darwinism. - I like it.
我对你的要求 只有一件事… 就是不要搞乱我的东西
All I ask from you, the one thing, is that you don't mess with my stuff.
说完了？
You done?
如果我搞搞小黑你会是什么感觉？
You know, how would you feel if I screwed with the Impala?
那将会是你生前做过的最后一件事
It'd be the last thing you ever did.
你动了他的电脑吗？
Did you take his computer?
像仆人一样的照顾他 我没有动
Serves him right, but no.
我是我弄丢的 因为我从来不弄丢东西
Well, I didn't lose it because I don't lose things.
哦 那没错 因为他是个完美先生
Oh, that's right, yeah, because he's Mr. Perfect.
好了 好了 为何你不告诉我接下来发生了什么？
Okay, okay. Why don't you just tell me what happened next?
还有一个受害者
There was one more victim.
我们也没有亲眼看到这个
Right. Now, we didn't see this one ourselves either.
我们是从证据中推断出来的 但是这个人
We kind of put it together from the evidence, but this guy, he was...
他是个科学家
He was a research scientist.
动物实验
Animal testing.
是的 没错 一个混蛋 符合标准
Yeah, you know, a dick. Which fits the pattern.
警察没有公布死因
The cops didn't release a cause of death...
因为他们对死因一无所知
because they had no clue what the cause was.
所以… 我们自己来查出来
So we checked it out ourselves.
嘿
Hey.
这一定很快
This ought to be quick.
好吧
Okay.
这真恶心
That is just nasty.
没错
Uh, yeah.
被分尸了？
Mutilated.
在我看来好象什么东西饿了
Looks to me like something was hungry.
- 他们确定他身份了吗？- 是的 一个大学里的科学家
- They identify him yet? - Yeah, a research scientist at the college.
顺便猜猜他的办公室在哪
Guess where his office was, by the way?
克劳福德礼堂 和那个教授一样
Crawford Hall, same as the professor.
那也是流氓男孩经历遭遇的地方
That's right where the frat boy had his close encounter.
是的
Yeah.
嘿 把那个东西拿给我
Hey, grab me the thing, would you?
谢谢
Thanks.
看到什么了？
What is it?
看起来像个…
Looks like a...
一片腹部鳞片
A belly scale?
一片腹部鳞片？什么东西的？
A belly scale? From what?
呃…
Uh...
鳄鱼的？
An alligator?
下水道中的鳄鱼 拜托
An alligator in the sewer? Come on.
怎么了 迪恩 这是个有名的城市传说
What? Well, Dean, it's a classic urban legend.
一个小孩把一条小鳄鱼从马桶冲下去…
A kid flushes a baby gator down the toilet...
然后它在下水道里面长成巨大的鳄鱼
and it grows huge in the tunnels.
但是还没有人找到过 那不是真的
Yeah, but no one's really ever found one. They're not real.
外星人的绑架也是 但是那小子的确发生了什么事
Well, neither is alien abduction but something chomped on this guy.
- 不会再比这个还奇怪的了 - 也许我们应该找个帮手
- This couldn't get any weirder. - Maybe we should get some help.
我会给鲍比打个电话 也许他从前遇到过类似的事
I'll call Bobby. Maybe he's run into something like this before.
哦 我保证他遇到过 给你上一堂典型的猎鬼课
I'm sure. Just your typical haunted-campus,
外星人绑架和下水道中的鳄鱼
alien-abduction, alligator-in-a-sewer gig.
是的 小菜一碟
Yeah, it's simple.
我们决定检查下水道
We decided to search the sewer anyway.
所以我们分头行动
So we split up, each taking one end of campus.
找到什么了？
Did you find anything?
是啊 只不过不是在下水道里
Yeah, I found something. Just not in the sewer.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
萨姆
Sam!
你认为这很有趣吗？
You think this is funny?
那要看是什么了？
It depends. What?
- 我的车 - 你的车怎么了？
- Heh, heh. The car. - What about the car?
你不能就这样把轮胎的气给放了 那会让钢圈坏掉的
You can't let the air out of the tires. You're gonna bend the rims.
哦 等等 我根本没靠近过你的车
Whoa, wait a minute. I didn't go near your car.
哦 是吗？那我怎么会找到这个的？
Oh, yeah. Huh. Then how'd I find this?
- 嘿 把钱还我 - 哦 不 不
- Hey, give me back my money. - Oh, no. No.
这就作为我的精神损失费吧
Consider it reparations for, uh, emotional trauma.
- 真好笑 把它还给我 - 不
- Yeah, very funny. Now give it back. - No.
迪恩 我会抢的
Dean, I have had it up to here with you.
是吗？那就放马过来吧
Yeah? Right back at you.
- 天啊 放开我 - 还给我
- God, get off me. - Give it back.
好了 我都听够了
Okay, I've heard enough.
两个小时后你就来了
You showed up about an hour after that.
我很惊讶 真的
I'm surprised at you two. I really am.
萨姆 迪恩没有偷你的电脑
Sam, first off, Dean did not steal your computer.
但我 嘘 嘘 嘘 嘘
- But I-There's...Shh.
迪恩 萨姆也没碰你的车
And, Dean, Sam did not touch your car.
是啊
Yeah.
如果你们还是为小事纠缠不清的话
And if you two bothered to pull your heads out of your asses...
那你们就别干了
it all would've been pretty clear.
- 什么？- 你们在查的事
- What? - What you're dealing with.
呃…
Uh...
- 什么也没有 - 我也是
- I got nothing. - Me neither.
你们也许碰到了一个骗子
You got a trickster on your hands.
- 我就是这么想的 - 什么？你才不是
- That's what I thought. - What? No you didn't...
我来告诉你们…
Well, I gotta tell you...
你们两个才是最大的线索
you guys were the biggest clue.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
这东西专搞恶作剧 就和呼吸一样简单
These things create chaos and mischief as easy as breathing.
就把你们搞糊涂了
And it's got you so turned around...
让你们胡思乱想
and at each other's throats, you can't even think straight.
- 电脑 - 轮胎
- The laptop. - The tires.
他知道你们找上他了
It knows you're onto him.
还把你们玩弄于股掌之间
And it's been playing you like fiddles.
那么它是什么 精神力量 魔鬼 还是什么？
So, what is it? Spirit, demon, what?
那是一种半人半神的东西
Well, more like demigods, really.
那是 洛基 在斯堪的纳维亚半岛
There's Loki in Scandinavia.
西非传说中的 安那西 成千上万
There's Anansi in West Africa. Dozens of them.
他们是不死的 他们能凭空创造东西
They're immortal and they can create things out of thin air.
和你我一样真实 也能让这些消失的无影无踪
Things as real as you and me. Make them vanish just as quick.
你说像恶魂 外星人 史前巨鳄
You mean, like an angry spirit or an alien, or an alligator.
受害者也符合它们的一贯标准
The victims fit the m.o. too.
骗子们喜欢瞄准位高权重者
Tricksters target the high and the mighty.
用一种近乎幽默的方式 把他们拉下谷地
Knock them down a peg, usually with a sense of humor.
死亡恶作剧
Deadly pranks, things like that.
鲍比 这些东西看上去像什么？
Bobby, what do these things look like?
大部分都是人形
Lots of things, but human mostly.
在我们认识的人中 哪个人一直关心此事呢？
And what human do we know who's been at ground zero this whole time?
哦 这个不错
Oh, that's a good one.
过来
Come here.
我能吃吗？我能吃 来
Could you eat? I could eat. Come on.
我缺了点什么
Something's missing.
恩
Mm!
抱歉 今天我很累 伙计们
Sorry I'm dragging a little ass today, boys.
昨天晚上忙了一晚
I had quite the night last night.
"做"了一晚 如果你抓住我话的重点
Lots of sex, if you catch my drift.
是啊 听着 我们不会久留的
Yeah, hard not to. Listen, we won't be long.
就检查下三楼的几间办公室
We just need to check a couple offices up on three.
没问题
No problem.
该死的 我把些东西忘在车里了
Oh, damn. I forgot something in the truck.
你知道是什么 我一会儿就来
You know what? I'll catch up with you guys.
好的
Okay.
就因为他读了几本世界周刊
Just because he reads Weekly World News...
不能说明他就是我们要找的人 你也读过了
doesn't mean he's our guy. You read it too.
我告诉你 就是他
I'm telling you, it's him.
我们还需要一些证据 就这些
I just think we need some hard proof. That's all.
鲍比还说过这些东西 有和昆虫一样的新陈代谢
Okay, Bobby mentioned that these suckers have a metabolism like an insect.
洁白的牙齿
All right, a real sweet tooth.
我没有发现任何糖果 甚至没有
I didn't find any candy bars or sugar. Not even Equal.
- 也许你还漏了什么 - 我从不漏东西的
- You missed something. - I don't miss things.
哦 对 你是"完美"先生
Oh, right because you're Mr. Perfect.
什么？你别把这骗子对我们的把戏 把气撒到我头上来？
What? Are you still pissed at me because of what the trickster did?
哦 算了吧 你在他出现之前就很跩了
Oh, come on, man. You been a tight ass long before that trickster showed up.
你就待在这儿 盯住那个看门人
Look, just stay here. Keep an eye on the janitor.
我要去他的住处
I'll go to his place, see if I can find any evidence...
在你鲁莽的用木桩扎他之前 先找到些证据
before you go barging in and staking the man.
等我回来 好吗？
Just wait till I get back, okay?
- 好吗？- 好
- Okay? - Okay.
见他的鬼去吧
Ah, screw this.
迪恩 我们一直在等你
We've been waiting for you, Dean.
哦 你们是真的
You guys aren't real.
相信我 那感觉也是真的
Trust me, sugar, it's gonna feel real.
来吧 让我们来给你按摩
Come on. Let us give you a massage.
啊
Wha...?
我一直不适合完美的结局 真的 我
You know, I'm a sucker for a happy ending. Really, I am...
但是… 还是算了吧
but I'm gonna have to pass.
他们是和平的礼物
They're a peace offering.
我知道你们兄弟两在干什么
I know what you and your brother do.
我以前也干过这事
I've been around a while, run into your kind before.
那你知道我… 不能让你再去害别人
Well, then you know that I can't let you just keep hurting people.
拜托
Come on.
这些人罪有应得
Those people got what was coming to them.
这些人作茧自缚
Hoisted on their own petards.
但你和萨姆 我喜欢你
But you and Sam, I like you. I do.
那是真的 所以还是好好的享受吧…
So treat yourself, long as you want.
多久都行 久到我去另外一个城市
Just long enough for me to move on to the next town.
- 是啊 我不能让你这么做 - 我本不想伤害你
- Yeah, I don't think I can let you do that. - I don't wanna hurt you.
而你知道我会的
And you know that I can.
伙计 我要告诉你 我欣赏你的风格 我的意思是
Look, man, I gotta tell you, I dig your style. All right? I mean...
真的 我的意思是 和外星人慢舞
I do, I mean, phew. And the slow-dancing alien?
- 那是我的最爱 - 是啊
- One of my personal favorites. - Yeah.
- 但我不能让你走 - 太令我失望了
- But I can't let you go. - Too bad.
我的确喜欢你
Like I said, I liked you.
萨姆是对的
Sam was right.
你不应该单独行动
You shouldn't have come alone.
那我同意你
Well, I'll agree with you there.
你们在外面吵架 那是个陷阱？
That fight you guys had outside, that was a trick?
恩
Hmm.
不错啊
Not bad.
但你想见识真正的把戏？
But you wanna see a real trick?
女士们 干的好
Ha! Nice toss, ladies.
表演得很好
Nice show.
迪恩…
Dean.
迪恩 迪恩 迪恩 我真不想这么做
Dean, Dean, Dean. I did not wanna have to do this.
我也是
Me neither.
你们还好吧？
You guys okay?
是的
Yeah.
没事
I guess.
我想说…
Well, I gotta say...
他真行
he had style.
- 谢谢你 鲍比 - 还是省省吧
- Bobby, thanks a lot. We couldn't have. - Hey, save it.
在有人发现他尸体前 我们快离开这里吧
Let's just get the hell out of Dodge before somebody finds that body.
好
Yeah.
听着 迪恩…
Look, Dean, um...
我只想说 我…
I just wanna say that I'm, uh...
嘿
Hey.
我也是
Me too.
你们真伤我的心 我们能快点儿离开吗？
You guys are breaking my heart. Could we please just leave?